Contact

latoyialatoyia@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/la-toyiajackson-msn-rn-ccrn-09074257 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Education
Leadership
Curriculum Development

La Toyia Jackson, MSN, RN, CCRN

Nursing Leadership

Greater Los Angeles Area

Summary

Experienced Professor Of Nursing with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in providing quality nursing education, coaching, team building, and curriculum development. Strong education professional with a MSN focused in nursing education from Walden University.

Experience

California Baptist University
Adjunct Professor
December 2018 - Present (1 year 7 months)

University of California Registered Nurse 2019 - Present (1 year)

Kaiser Permanente Department Administrator 2017 - 2019 (2 years)

West Coast University Nursing Professor October 2010 - 2018 (8 years)

Riverside County Regional Medical Center Manager Agency Education 2015 - 2016 (1 year)

LOMA LINDA VETERANS ASSOCIATION FOR RESEARCH AND EDUCATION

Critical Care Nurse Educator 2013 - 2015 (2 years)

Education

Azusa Pacific University

Doctor of Philosophy (PhD), Nursing Education · (2019 - 2022)

Walden University
BSN, MSN/Ed, Education · (2007 - 2010)

Chaffey College
Associate of Science (A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2003 - 2005)